{
    "subject": "resource/Leonard_Susskind",
    "predicate": "ontology/field",
    "object": "resource/Physics",
    "human_readable": "Leonard Susskind's field of expertise is Physics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9368194937705994,
            "question": "Is Leonard Susskind a physicist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067749977111816,
            "question": "What is Leonard Susskind's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891069233417511,
            "question": "Leonard Susskind is an expert in what branch of science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8429768681526184,
            "question": "What field of study does Leonard Susskind specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8411363363265991,
            "question": "What is Leonard Susskind's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7889624238014221,
            "question": "What subject is Leonard Susskind known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257897019386292,
            "question": "In which science does Leonard Susskind work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5707142353057861,
            "question": "What academic discipline does Leonard Susskind belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5477654933929443,
            "question": "What is the main focus of Leonard Susskind's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5346960425376892,
            "question": "What kind of research does Leonard Susskind likely conduct?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leonard Susskind's field of expertise is Physics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main focus of Leonard Susskind's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What academic discipline does Leonard Susskind belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which science does Leonard Susskind work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7806_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention Leonard Susskind as a renowned theoretical physicist, and one of the fathers of string theory. There are multiple mentions of his work and research interests in physics, which supports the triple that he is an expert in Physics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Leonard Susskind\u2019s contributions to theoretical physics, his roles such as a professor at Stanford University and researcher in areas like string theory and quantum mechanics. These details support the statement that Leonard Susskind's field of expertise is Physics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}